Okay. So, I'm recording on both screens
and you can tell because there is an
orange dot in the top right of both the
phone and the iPad and the iPad
screenshot was taken after the phone
screenshot. Um, sound waves are the
easiest to rec uh to to think of the
abstract of how to prove ownership, but
um images are likely much easier if you
crop out the surrounding
Or if you put a border
um around the outside of really really
small width, okay, just three
a three pixel black border around the
thing um it's going to alter the
picture.
But if you can cut out both middles of
your picture and the other pictures and
and yours makes sense visually, it can
be predicted what it is. Or maybe you
can describe what it is and the computer
will match it to some fuzzy feature.
Or maybe it can ask you a series of
questions. Uh is this what you're
talking about? Is this another one of
the thing you're talking about? Um
or colors? I don't know. That's why the
image is just kind of hard. Um what do
you do? Just give the interior image. I
guess you have a huge image and you just
give them like the middle of it then.
Okay. But can people create different
images that make sense in that area? So
I don't know. Um I guess they could make
you can never match the waveform. So you
cut out some because in um
in sound there's the idea of a of a wave
form um where it's like yep, this is the
exact same one. Um,
even if the volume's changed, I think
you'd have to distort the song
in the recording in order for the
waveform to be different. Um, I think
the waveform always kind of looks like
the archetype of itself. Um,
is it just stretched and curved like can
you change the wavelength it the
waveform itself of a song? That'd be a
good question.
or of audio
recorded at certain interval intervals.
Um, so what we could do is we could pull
up the clock.
I'll do that.
On the other on the iPad. So, I'm going
to pull up the clock.
One thing I hate is these apps are so
hard to Oh, come on. There it goes. For
a second it wasn't going to go.
There it is. There's a stopwatch and all
the lap things.
I can't do that on my phone,
but I can say lap one go. You know, the
beginning of of the otter
recording
being timed happened 20 seconds ago
right now.
So 20 seconds ago right now.
4515.
Sorry. 4815.
4845.
I can't do that on my phone. I think I
can't do that on my phone. Got recorded.
Okay. So, there's lap one. I think this
thing got recorded here at this time.
So, when I say that, that's a that's a
synchronization symbol. So, you have to
go back and synchronize. No.
Oh, there's nothing there.
Is this the craziest gift you've ever
seen?
Or if it's not a gift, is it a video?
And so the longer the GIF is, you have
to post a GIF.
And then common sense people have to be
able to perform a mathematical
transaction of some sort uh if they
watch the whole thing and they'll have
had to collect clues from throughout.
And the puzzle will be created by
anybody who wants to create the puzzle
and then they'll they'll shout about why
their puzzle is cool. And when people
fill out their puzzle, they get the
profits for the next like they get a
bonus when people figure out their
puzzle or their puzzle contains the most
information.
um that's correct and accurate.
And I think we can reward people that
tell the truth or have consistent
answers at least with um more evidence
as to who who is. So the people when the
same when a different when the same
question is an asked in the future we're
going to give the same answer or at
least the one that will have developed
according to time.
Let's say we have to post like what's
your weight and I say I'm right now I'm
about 206
and I'm way overweight. I could lose
about 20 pounds and I'd be great and
that's the direction I want to go. And
so I have to tell the truth about my
weight and my age. I think I'm going
just say I'm 30.
And there's my demographic.
And um that's me. Hi,
my name is blah blah blah. Um
here's my introduction.
Be cool if you could just type lapse
while you record and it would
put links together and make screenshots
and everything like that's that's what I
want to do. these little
prove ownership of this recording. This
is like a digital
it's it's a live recording of one
thought
and I'm talking to an audience
that I don't know will ever listen
and I'm trying to think things that
aren't too crazy that will help
everybody and helping everybody and
making me lots of money like Bo Burnham
said feels pretty good otherwise life is
pretty depressing. Love helps too,
which is the message of that movie.
Message of Bo Burnham. Uh, lap four.
That's how we'll do it.
Lap four start. Okay. So, you say lap
four and it gets tied to the
time stamp. So, I I should have said lap
three there and it would have been 357.
And that's the end of it. So, you go
back to the previous lap from that. And
then this is kind of the app I wanted to
build. In fact, this is probably what
I'll build on Mac. Um, something like
this.
It's helpful for my thoughts. Um, it
will help me bookmark thoughts and and
chapter them off. And I mean, not being
rude or I guess, yeah, I'm absolutely
being very egotistical.
It's kind of what the Bible was.
It's a set of self-referential
sayingings, stories, stories,
allegorories, advices, laws, rules,
recommendations,
um,
uh, warnings.
Haven't read it. Probably should.
Boring,
boring stuff. Who cares? also self
self-referential in some ways. So,
that's interesting. Um, I've been told
it's even a book of curses, which
I feel like that's how things like the
Illuminati start. So, I'm going to stay
away from that. It gives me the
heebie-jebies.
Heb's lap four.
Here's
something self-referential. It's trying
to be
it's it's a self-referential
thing. Here's the actual screenshot
itself. So, it'll be on the iPad and we
can take a screenshot of the iPad
receiving it. So, that'll be pretty fun.
Uh oh. No bugs. No bugs. No bugs.
There's a flash. Got to stop recording
the screen now.
We'll attach another if it's good.
I'll share this with Otter at least.
Yep. Got to cut this off.
Okay, I'm cutting off on iPad screen
recording
and editing said recording
as soon as possible. It's not ready yet.
It was pretty long.
How long was it?
Where's the clock? Jesus.
Here's the clock. I mean, this is a
provable time stamp.
It proves I was recording when the thing
happened.
Verifiable events equal trustworthy
nodes.
Proving trustworthy events. Proving
verifiable events.
There's a lap. Um the screen recording
is still not still not done.
Uh, there it is. 2010. It's done. I'm
editing it now.
Can I take screenshots here?
Yep.
Can't even tell what that bottom one is.
Should probably zoom in, but
I think that's pretty good.
movie I've been talking about provable
provable provable that's why anonymity
is important so that we can continue
these provable things
I wouldn't want to share this much if I
wasn't anonymous
editing now not screen recording
okay
there's only 20 minutes and 10 seconds
let's see what we revealed here. Um, if
anybody caught it in a live stream,
please don't look at it.
I don't know. I got to pay you some form
of profits.
If I shared profits, would you trust me?
And that's what shares are. And a
trustee, I mean, that's literally what
they're for.
Oh,
we might not actually
be revealing anything.
No, we did
50.
It's 60884 that we start revealing.
is 1943.
The preview shows up in 1943.
Oh, it's got text. Yep. Yep. Yep. We're
in 1945 is where we're going to cut.
No. 1942
happens at 1943.
1942.
Um,
which is 7 6:07 on the clock.
I think I did it. Now I'm at 11:46 on my
timer. My stopwatch, sorry, I should
say.
1942. I think that sounds right.
Interesting.
Pulled up the uh what time I pulled up
the clock.
I pulled up the clock at I'm going to
change to
screens here in a second.
Give you the time. I started recording
around 14 minutes in the recording. 4909
on the otter.
And 20 seconds ago,
the largest thing we could see
was 4814.
So really, you could see
Oh my god. Stupid thing didn't stop.
song in the recording.
Song and the recording. In order for the
waveform to be different, I think the
waveform always kind of looks like the
archetype of itself.
And then when I
which is what is that record at certain
intervals
that's like four lines up in the longest
thing.
Um anyway,
just hear the hum. It's terrible.
It's these electronics,
but I'm using them
hopefully to my gain.
Okay, this is pulled up at 4421.
I don't know what that means.
You know what?
First thing you see here is at 26
seconds
and the stopwatch
It's 4909 at the very top of the screen.
It's the only cell showing.
Right. There's our final
synchronization. I don't know how.
There it is.
Pride and joy right there.
There's the middle. There's the outside.
And there's the single thing right
there. I'm not going to draw too many.
Here's the single box.
Single box.
You train an algorithm on that
and you are good.
Um, I think I can screen record again.
The issue's been resolved.
Whether I should screen record again or
not is the other question.
I'm getting pretty recursive now.
So, that's fun.
We can do one of these
and then share it with the
No, we can't
I would have to edit it.
Yeah, got to cut that. So, another cut
is before 1657.
So, a cut would just be um the stop is
not going to be the main button.
Um you can do angles here.
What in the world is this?
Cuz there's 100 milliseconds in 60
seconds.
Wow.
Anyway, the UI for my recording app is
going to be like this. Um,
that's just don't feel in the right
spot. Um,
so now can you write reduce time down to
an angle?
Because you're not you just have to look
at the angle. Um, and you could probably
honestly speed this up, but you could
look at the angle that the recording's
at, and that's the only thing that's
editable.
Um, and you'd have to override that to
um
to say the entire time. It's not
convenient to say the time. you say the
angle and then it's when you say it, you
say the angle and then it knows where it
is in a time and then it's going to look
back
for that angle. They only have to count
so many um the frequency divided by the
number of seconds of a cycle.
I don't know, something like that. um
that will reduce down your sample size.
Um and you can you can detect that um
using you don't even need machine
learning. You need a computer vision
model. Um
so let's upload this.
No, I can't.
Did I stop that recording?
I said I had to edit it.
Jesus Christ.
Another lap.
They're both milliseconds. One's the
lap.
One's the seconds of the minute.
Every lap, my angle's going to change.
Oh my god.
This is modulo arithmetic
applied to proof of ownership.
If you're creating something on a
screen,
you can Oh, excuse me. You can perform
various actions
that
will
prove that you own that content. And and
now what we can do is we can reward that
content.
We can reward that content
by applying
rewards
of
holders of the guesses of the silly
question such as what's the ratio of
blue laps to orange laps
during this recording.
You can't tell just by looking. You
can't tell just by looking at the laps.
You'd have to use math. You can't just
know.
So, you just need to apply a simple
formula really. Um, I don't know what it
is and it hurts my brain to think about
it, but it's simple.
Um,
you just have to figure it out.
And I don't And that's a second minute
on this lap.
Minutes about to elapse. But I wouldn't
have known that without looking at it.
um without looking at the number of
minutes that have elapsed.
Um
mesmerizing really.
So if I do a lap here at 15 seconds,
oop, sorry, it's going to be at 30
seconds here. Then the orange is behind.
Okay. Did I get that? Yeah, I got that.
So, let's diagnose this. What's going on
here? There's eight laps.
Uh, blue is ahead, but I lapped at
I already did a lap here. So, I'm at I'm
on the ninth lap.
The eighth lap is um
the eighth lap is um
I didn't lap. Took the screenshot. I
didn't press lap. screenshot should
trigger a lap as well. And a lap should
trigger trigger a screenshot. Um, and
that screenshot should be saved as the
bookmark
of where you were so you can look. Um,
I screenshotted. We have a few different
ratios here.
What is the 35 10 15 20 25 30?
What is that?
Is that the minutes?
What?
What is that? 05
minutes in the hour.
If it is like something 25,
it's 56.
I just realized I don't know how to read
this clock.
It's 2 minutes later. 30 minutes and a
half hour.
What is it now?
24 minutes past the half hour. Is it 54?
Oh my gosh. That's minutes past the half
hour.
Wow, that makes so much more sense than
doing it on the same diagonal. Then you
can say seconds, not the minutes. And so
people don't have to multiply when they
when they think about time. The most
common time. It's how many seconds, not
how many minutes.
One, two, three. Like, which one's
bigger? Five or eight?
Eight. Why does it matter? Oh, yeah.
because we're 8 times 5 seconds and a
12th of a minute. It's very confusing to
like just think off the bat, but you
look at this for one second, you say 25
past the half hour.
Um, and you don't really care about what
hour it is. Like, we're timing stuff. We
don't I don't care if it's 12:30 or
2:30.
Um,
is that what that is? 25:08. Oh, and
it's also just a stopwatch. So, it's
saying 25, which is the minutes past the
half hour,
15, 16, 17, 18, 19,
and they're both going. The orange is
the time, and the blue is my lap, and
that's all I know. Um,
this would have been really boring to
watch.
So, how long was I just showing a a
stopwatch going on the GIF?
Um
here
the videos.
God damn it. Stop recording. God
I would have to edit it.
I need to get better at editing and not
do this on my iPad.
I can't find any
Who are you?
Oh my god.
No way.
It's not complete. 1029. Wait. Yeah, it
is.
Was that one too?
Oh my god, that's a 20 minute video.
Just since it both of them received at
107,
one's a m one's an MP4. I don't think
that matters.
Okay.
Wow. Look at my movie.
Good projects. Okay.
Create new movie
libraries photos.
They let me go to a not place.
Laptop
downloads.
Oh my god. It's called
1259.
This is the risky one.
Move these boat to the desk.
on the iPad. So, I'm going to pull up
the clock.
One thing I hate is these apps are so
hard to Oh, come on. There it goes. For
a second it wasn't going to go.
There it is. There's a stopwatch and
I'll lap things.
I can't do that on my phone.
screen record again or not is the other
question
they call sentence interpretation. Do
you understand that? Just
Are you waiting?
>> Well,
record again.
what they call sentence interpretation.
Do you understand that?
Good.
What are you writing down?
>> Well,
record again or not is the other
question
I'm getting.
It's a gift. It's teaching me things.
screen recording or not is the other
question.
to the girl with the mousy hair,
but her mommy is yelling
and daddy,
but her friend is nowhere to be seen.
Now she walks through her sunken dream
to the seat with the clearest view
and she's hooked to the silver screen.
But the bell is a sadd
but she's lifted 10 times or more.
She could spit in the eyes of fools
as they ask her to focus on
hiding in the dance hall. Oh man, look
at those ging.
It's a freaky show.
Take a look at
the wrong guy.
Wonder if you'll ever know
who's the best.
Is there life on Mars?
It's on tortured brows.
Now the workers are struck for
lemons on sale again.
See the mice in their million hordes.
From my people to the north of
who pretend is out of bounds
to my mother, my dog and clowns,
but the film is a sro.
It's about to be a game
as I ask you to go someday
in the dance hall. Oh man.
Take a look.
Wonder if you'll ever know
who's in the bestelling show
on
I just want to touch on two issues I've
come across with Proton Mail over the
last
two days,
couple hours.
Notice this is all of my personal
information.
Well, I can talk through it. The problem
is that I've
deleted I've attempted to delete um
addresses.
If you disable them, they don't go away.
there's no way to delete an address. So,
I'm going to email them about that. If
there's not, I'm going to be very
frustrated because then you have to keep
knowing like what your anonymous
identity would you want it to be and
that's kind of not the point.
Um,
just realized we can do an anonymous
email.
Provably anonymous, I think.
Yeah, you could just
I don't know. You could do it. It's too
complicated to explain right now. But
anyway, so there's that. And two, I want
to be prrated on this. Um, now I will
say another issue is that
the UI is terrible. So, I click add
address in the settings screen
for identity and addresses. I click add
address. It's got my user, which I don't
know how to change, but that's okay for
now. Um, not my address.
Uh,
something random. Blah blah.
There's no indication, which I think
there should be
um that that address is taken. This is a
very especially if the refund doesn't
come through um or the delete if it does
if I can't actually delete my emails.
Um now I understand that deleting emails
is a technically challenging problem.
What do you do with the emails that go
to there? What if there's credit card
bills? Are you liable? I don't know. Um
but there should be a way. I was trying
to take
a certain
email
and couldn't get it um because well it's
already taken apparently
I'm going to stop recording.
enable
dark mode.
Enable dark mode.
>> Okay, I turned on dark mode.
Hey Siri.
Uh-huh.
What are your preferences?
Show preferences.
Hey Siri.
Hey Siri. Send a message.
Hey Siri. How's the weather today?
Hey Siri, what does the rest of my day
look like?
Hey Siri, play some music.
>> Hi, I'm Siri.
>> Hi, I'm Siri. Hi, I'm Siri.
>> Hi, I'm Siri. Choose the voice you'd
like me to use.
>> Hey, Siri.
>> Uh-huh.
>> Yes,
>> that's what I figured.
I like it when we get along.
>> You're way too positive.
up.
Oh, well.
Turn on dictation mode.
>> Dictation is already on.
>> Hello. Hello.
Hello. Hello.
Open accessibility.
If I use voice control, will it type?
dictation mode.
Hello.
Hello. Hello. Hello.
Testing recording
dictation mode.
Hello.
There we go.
Hello. Can I type now?
Can I type in a note?
Dictation mode.
Why does it keep forgetting whether or
not it's in dictation mode?
How long does dictation mode stay open?
Can I use dictation mode when the app is
in the background?
How about when the app is reforgrounded?
Yep. So, that's good.
Do a note, not a notion.
It's a godful
girl,
but her mommy is yelling
and her daddy has told her to go,
but Her friend is nowhere to be seen.
Now she walks through her sunken dream
to the seats with the clearest view.
And she's hooked to the silver screen.
But the film is a sadded
10 times or more.
She could spit in the eyes of fools
as they as her to focus on
hiding in the dance hall. Where?
Turn off voice control.
>> Okay, I turned off voice control.
Oh yeah.
Still don't know what I was waiting for.
And my time is running wild.
I'm still recording.
Oh, wow.
That's the whole thing. Was I recording
the screen, too? Oh my god. I'm going to
stop that now.